trades on saturday scheduled transport the sit and wait monastery position panic in
周六交易预定运输坐等寺院恐慌
this video julien's auctions out of six nations by jasmin strategies to
这段视频朱利安（Julien）通过茉莉花策略在六个国家进行的拍卖，
have many ways to change the increasingly profit and with wings at
有很多方法可以改变日益增长的利润，
let's jump ride in is now stepping into general options trading jobs one by one
现在让我们跳入正逐步进入一般期权交易工作的行列中
principle of these general guidelines of polo looking at potential trader joe's
马球看待潜在交易者乔的这些一般指导原则的原理
filler is impulses knapsack judgment day trader us army in the
填充物是冲动背负审判日美军在
focus not be on any trade off stage iv christian opening the best possible
第四阶段不要专注于任何权衡取舍
trade trade and trust for more important your goodness judgment day long next
贸易贸易和信任对于您的善意判断更为重要，这一天将持续很长时间
topmodel trade plan b traded note curriculum trade plans the cassiopeia
topmodel贸易计划b交易票据课程贸易计划仙后座
account for everything possible trader joe's los angeles die straight plan
考虑到所有可能的交易者乔的洛杉矶死定计划
great pleasure of the following questions first we like it against me
首先对以下问题感到非常高兴，我们喜欢反对我
season section strategies in excel the eccentric straight ohlsson times
擅长使用偏心直线奥尔森时间的赛季分段策略
technically well going que superior justice voltis impulse
技术上很好的高级司法沃尔蒂斯的冲动
mobility is tested with the options position some time before the expiration
在到期前的某个时间使用选项头寸测试移动性
significant is the trick with display up to wi inspected paypal baltic sea pipeline
重要的是显示与无线检查的贝宝波罗的海管道有关的技巧
is so the crisis has come just with magic is taking on edition this is that
所以危机就随着魔术而来了，这就是
new make sense it is the part of the features things position is already
新的意义，这是事物位置已经存在的功能的一部分
limited downside risk was in living room for web site at risk of strangers with 1
有限的下行风险是网站客厅中的陌生人风险为1
before were constituted east success for example of duty justin and how to
之前曾在东方取得成功，例如贾斯汀的职责以及如何
in Vienna student Kristin give yourself motogp right at the end of using the
在维也纳的学生克里斯汀（Kristin）在使用完
swan in which the break even point figure out the things and increasing the
天鹅，其中盈亏平衡点指出事物并增加了
rhythm and only just in time just came down freenet loans moment des late
节奏，只有及时才从免费网络贷款中降下来
Last but not least two ways of self assessment is had to fishermen for
最后但并非最不重要的两种自我评估方法是渔民
capital july in tones woofer judgment it is
首都七月中低音扬声器判断它是
simple monastery position and open in part i knew physical server for justice
简单的修道院位置，部分开放，我知道正义的物理服务器
schotten craig said the way i do it for you in utah jazz with of the straight
斯科特·克雷格（Schotten craig）说道我在犹他爵士音乐节中为您做的方式
to make sense that deadly strategies is only going on with technology for your content
可以说致命的策略只会随着内容技术的发展而变化
security strategies and construction chemicals will end this word profile
安全策略和建筑化学品将结束此词汇表
on their account looks like dancin shoes sales professionals of the online strange
在他们的帐户上看起来像是网上的dancin鞋销售专业人士，很奇怪
from possible jobs with bwin the online price bridges wolf of the strike before he
从bwin的可能工作中，在线奖赏弥合了罢工前的狼
they hold your account the culprit is this from lowe's people you have to come
他们掌握了您的帐户，罪魁祸首是来自Lowe的人，您必须来
endlessly intuitive weight watchers share condor is simply foulte testes are time
无休止的直观体重观察者分享秃鹰简直就是肮脏的睾丸
disneys up to break even point and increased software range differences of
迪士尼达到收支平衡点并增加了软件范围的差异
online price on his account and software with seven dollars sven jubt
他的帐户和软件的网上价格为七美元，斯文·贾特（Sven Jubt）
rebell call spread to the one heart and one at fifteen strikes this hot
叛逆的呼声传到了一颗心，十五点一击，这很热
pursuit also the dissident send the european project origin of it and
追求也持不同政见者发送它的欧洲项目的起源和
drop and even with the tail risk increased is direct because it continues like
下降，即使尾巴风险增加也是直接的，因为它像
before for justin principal at redefin alien the video so what i do instead
之前在Justin校长重新定义外星人视频之前，我该怎么做
they just have an account high time church the online first price me
他们只是有一个帐户高时间教会网上优先给我
treat a district spokesman one side on their account at the münsterischer klose
在克罗斯（Münsterischerklose）的账目上一方面对待地区发言人
for gomez according to his technique text tape on exact take profit in antiquity
戈麦斯根据他的技术文字录音带准确了解了上古的获利情况
time a collection premium selling valid spokesman for the leyens price
收取溢价，以有效的价格出售有效的发言人
That was Christopher Reeve Scanning's biggest beneficiary of the break even point
那是克里斯托弗·里夫·斯金宁（Christopher Reeve Scanning）收支平衡点的最大受益者
figure out in the world is win win win situation here is kharkov on the
弄清楚世界上是双赢局面，这里是哈尔科夫
otherwise an account costs unrealistic that justin is technik
否则，帐户花费不大，因为贾斯汀是技术人员
half of the profit range model is paid at the alliance price of the way back
利润范围模型的一半是按返程的联盟价格支付的
it might not be optimal this was schütten john corrigan s long
这可能不是最佳选择，这是SchüttenJohn Corrigan的长
as you stayed on this part of jobs with credit risk in christa profit
当您呆在这部分工作中时，克里斯塔（Christa）的利润存在信用风险
the six exchange simple goods test online price to make these specific examples of
六个交易所简单商品测试在线价格，以使这些具体示例
single just one of the seas price mues ob and beyond borders die opposition bei
唯一的海洋价格暴行之一，ob and oborders死于反对派bei
berg drive put option and sell new or at one trade dispute price june is a
berg drive看跌期权和新的或以一个贸易纠纷价格出售6月是
lucky day to expressive price massive only solid roll out put option once
幸运的一天，表现力巨大的价格只有一次坚实的推出看跌期权
again the pr-professional of the new positions lay until he became a goal of the strict
再次担任新职位的专业人士，直到他成为严格的目标
separate street spirit of the same strike price discount call option
具有相同行使价折扣看涨期权的独立街头精神
it will give you the tie your screen ad credits put option piontek price of the
它将使您的屏幕广告点数投放选项的价格与piontek的价格保持一致
collection doing so is cult minor kills shading defined research des
收集这样做是邪教未成年人杀死阴影定义研究des
Electric motor accounts are only required with the post world net credit strategy
仅邮政世界净信用策略才需要电动机帐户
europe's best time is the credit spread internally an account for the simplicity of the
欧洲最好的时机是信贷的内部分散，这是简化交易的原因。
online first is basically trading for 100 dollars
网上第一笔交易的价格为100美元
Each cell kohl funny jumps and xv you an account
每个单元格kohl有趣的跳跃和xv您一个帐户
in dc fix traffic light cooled for the same one writes a low rating model a
在直流固定交通灯冷却为同一人写一个低评级模型
view to black premium and day which christin krischke was profit potential
查看黑溢价和克里斯汀·克里斯切克（Christin Krischke）获利的日子
the break even point monzingen of the uni traders is the budget crisis software
单一交易者的盈亏平衡点monzingen是预算危机软件
the most relaxed time to do this the door handles that justins the video immediately home
最轻松的时间做到这一点，门把手立即将视频带回家
this is a sensation
这是一种感觉
for justin, the egyptian andre lenz is the prize
对于贾斯汀，埃及人安德烈·伦茨（Andre lenz）是获奖者
the video is on position in credit easing trail is in possible fishing
该视频处于放宽信贷的位置，有可能钓鱼
june relatively cdu opposition unicredit is open and bmj
6月相对cdu反对派unicredit是开放和bmj
credit change of the creation center
创建中心的信用变更
trading the pop star
交易流行歌星
david hughes of justin technik presents early and the short call
贾斯汀技术公司的大卫休斯（Justin Hughes）提出了早期和短期呼吁
option bot problems is the i like you one connect premium sd slot is a
选项机器人的问题是我喜欢你一个连接溢价SD插槽是
premium often in the options green state, christel is in part position in lütter
溢价通常在期权绿色状态中，christel在lütter中处于部分位置
option must be built into the extra ration ship for today otherwise expiration with
选件必须内置到今天的额外配给船中，否则到期日为
Strikepreis die pens and hamas premier contact usually make sense of the new
罢工的钢笔和哈马斯总理的联系通常使新的意义
positions online trading price for the asics traffic light since the ancient strike in
自上古罢工以来，为asics红绿灯设置在线交易价格
the expressions are you want to 100 fixed strike price is the display
表达式是您想要的100固定执行价格是显示
professional knowledge jobs jobs kyrgyz timo days to work out the world in crises
专业知识工作工作吉尔吉斯提莫天在危机中锻炼世界
gries promotion of the jazz band had to break even know where to do they justify
爵士乐队的gries促销员必须收支平衡，知道他们在哪里做辩护
class price
班级价格
for inspiration how controlling upgrade is great weekend extent of the most
寻求灵感如何控制升级是最重要的周末活动
important persons in that can help is driving trade and winning ford's and
重要的人可以帮助推动贸易并赢得福特和
Heimste capital job centers whether can be used the two elsewhere in the alpine
海姆斯特资本工作中心是否可以在高山的其他地方使用
the ground is brought to the us band the others can be very help by checking
地面带到了美国乐队，其他人可以通过检查获得很大帮助
world trading performance of the chief of deep exchange finished read term this
深度交易负责人的全球交易表现读完本
video she said yeah yeah yeahs with principles for youtube follow me and you
她说的影片，是的，YouTube的原则，是的，跟着我，你
make sure to like buttons dispute
确保喜欢按钮的争议